

SAMIR AHMED

Address: Dubai,UAE Phone: 0502071018

Email: samiromarahmed@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am an Arabic and Islamic educator with a Bachelor's Degree and 13 years of teaching experience. I have taught in Dubai and Egypt, focusing on Arabic and Islamic Studies. Currently, I work as an Islamic Studies instructor at RAFFLES WORLD ACADEMY, emphasizing a nurturing teaching style.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Raffles World Academy

Aug 2015 - Present

- · Arabic A&B Teacher.
- · Islamic A&B Teacher.
- Islamic Deputy HoD.

Gems Millennium School Dubai

Aug 2011 - Jul2015

- Arabic B Teacher for non-Arab students.
- · Responsible for creating curriculum.

Jaber Ansari Modern School, Cairo

Jun2006 - Jul 2011

- · Arabic A teacher.
- · Islamic A teacher.
- Responsible for Middle school Arabic assessment.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Arabic and Islamic Studies.

Aug 2000 - May 2004

Faculty of Education, Tanta University

Major in Arabic and Islamic Studies

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

- ICDL-UN
- · Teaching strategies, 21 century formula -KHDA
- Leadership program Gems Education
- Train the trainer program Gems Education
- operational planning and evaluation Gems Education
- PYP teaching and learning Raffles World Academy
- The Pedagogy Training Program for Teachers Emirates College for Advanced Education
- Emotional Intelligence Emirates College for Advanced Education
- Authentic assessment Emirates College for Advanced Education
- Collaborative Learning Emirates College for Advanced Education
- Teaching students with low Academic Performance Emirates College for Advanced Education
- Certified Microsoft Innovative Educator Microsoft

REFERENCES

Hanadi Al Zaaby

- Arabic HoD
- Raffles World Academy
- HanadiZ@rwadubai.com
- 0503265880

Mohammed Elsayed

- Islamic HoD
- Raffles World Academy
- MohammedA@rwadubai.com
- 0508786105